"KASABA DOKTORU"
-Doctor...
-Can you do it?
There is a patient who came here
before these patients...
...with a COPD history, suffering
from shortness of breath...
...showing indications of SIRS,
highly possible pneumonia.
SIRS: BODILY REACTION
TO THE INFECTION INJURIES.
Did you check her vitals?
It is 72%, pretty stable,
but she has a COPD history...
Then do your job!
We're in the ER right now!
"KASABA DOKTORU"
We should check her chest,
or check her blood gas at least.
Do you know how to read?
What does it say there? Emergency.
Look, his BP is going down!
Whose case is more urgent?
She might have sepsis,
is this not urgent?
SEPSIS: BLOOD POISONING.
If you don't do what you're told,
don't waste my time. Get out!
You're ignoring the danger
right under your nose!
"KASABA DOKTORU"
Okay. First, calm down.
Do a blood ultrasound
in case of hemoperitoneum.
HEMOPERITONEUM:
GASTRIC BLEEDING.
Then, stabilize his vitals,
and wait for me.
Don't move the iron rod.
Do you hear me?
Don't you dare!
I'll remove it.
Okay, sir. Understood.